buying a home especially your first home
is both exciting and stressful you've
got a lot of decisions to make detached
home or a condo closer to work or closer
to schools the biggest decision of all
how to pay for your home usually you
have to decide between a mortgage with a
great rate or flexible features but with
manualized bank select you don't have to
choose an either/or mortgage instead you
get a great rate and great features
flexible options let you choose a
payment schedule that matches your cash
flow take advantage of generous
prepayment options to pay down your
mortgage faster choose a fixed or
variable rate a fixed rate is locked in
for a specific length of time many
people choose a fixed rate if they are
concerned that rates may go up or if
they like knowing that their payment
will be for a set period of time a
variable rate on the other hand is often
lower than fixed rates but will go up or
down along with changes in your lenders
prime rate you may choose a variable
rate to lower your interest costs if you
think interest rates will remain the
same or even decrease in future you can
choose a mortgage term as short as six
months or as long as 10 years and if you
need help just talk to us if you also
get a menu life bank account that pays a
high rate of interest plus accessing
your money is easy with mobile banking
he transfers point-of-sale purchases and
thousands of fee free ABMS most
mortgages are what they are but Manulife
banks select as a mortgage that's right
for you
[Music]